Inventory of the William R. Kintner papers, 1951-1986
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1951-1986 (Folder 59-89)
  - Palmer, Norman D., 1971-1972 (Folder 61: 4)
  - Perlmutter, Amos, 1968-1971 (Folder 61: 5)
  - Petrov, Vladimir, 1968-1970 (Folder 61: 6)
  - Petrovskiĭ, Vladimir, 1969-1971 (Folder 61: 7)
  - Philadelphia Committee on Foreign Relations, 1969-1973 (Folder 61: 8)
  - Pipes, Richard, 1972 (Folder 61: 9)
  - Ploss, Sidney, 1971-1972 (Folder 61: 10)
  - Possony, Stefan, 1970-1973 (Folder 61: 11-12)
    - 1970-1971 (Folder 61: 11)
    - 1972-1973 (Folder 61: 12)
  - Ra'anan, Uri, 1971-1973 (Folder 62: 1)
  - Reitz, Curtis R., 1971 (Folder 62: 2)
  - Richardson, Robert C., 1969-1973 (Folder 62: 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1958-1973 (Folder 62: 4)
  - Rostow, Walt W., 1971-1972 (Folder 62: 5)
  - Rubinstein, Alvin Z., 1970-1972 (Folder 62: 6)
  - Salet, Eugene A., 1968-1971 (Folder 62: 7)
  - Saltzman, Charles E., 1967-1971 (Folder 62: 8)
  - Sammartino, Peter, 1971-1973 (Folder 62: 9)
  - Sauvant, Karl Peter, 1971-1972 (Folder 62: 10)
  - Schaetzel, J. Robert, 1968-1973 (Folder 62: 11)
  - Schmidt, Adolph W., 1967-1970 (Folder 62: 12)
  - Scott, Harriet Fast, 1967-1969 (Folder 62: 13)
  - Haig, Alexander M., Jr., 1971-1973 (Folder 62: 14)
  - Hamilton, Natalie Wales, 1963-1968 (Folder 62: 15)
  - Hanks, Nancy, 1958-1972 (Folder 62: 16)
  - Hannon, Stuart L., 1971 (Folder 63: 1)
  - Harlow, Bryce, 1963-1973 (Folder 63: 2)
  - Harnwell, Gaylord P., 1969-1973 (Folder 63: 3)
  - Harrington, David, 1972 (Folder 63: 4)
  - Harvey, Mose L., 1971-1973 (Folder 63: 5)
  - Hassner, Pierre, 1971-1972 (Folder 63: 6)
  - Hester, Donald, 1970-1973 (Folder 63: 7)
  - Hobstetter, John N., 1970-1971 (Folder 63: 8)
  - Hook, Sydney, 1972 (Folder 63: 9)
  - Host Enterprises, 1971-1972 (Folder 63: 10)
  - House Committee on Foreign Affairs, 1968 (Folder 63: 11)
  - Hudson Institute, 1970-1973 (Folder 63: 12)
  - Institute for Strategic Studies, 1969-1973 (Folder 64: 1)
  - Inter-American Defense College, 1970-1972 (Folder 64: 2)
  - Inter-American Development Bank, 1968-1970 (Folder 64: 3)
  - Intercollegiate Review, 1970-1973 (Folder 64: 4)
  - International Studies Association, 1970-1972 (Folder 64: 5)
  - Israeli consulate, New York City, 1970-1972 (Folder 64: 6)
  - Iungerich, Raphael, 1973 (Folder 64: 7)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1970-1972 (Folder 64: 8)
  - James, Daniel, 1970-1972 (Folder 64: 9)
  - Janda, Kenneth, 1970-1971 (Folder 64: 10)
  - Janosik, Edward G., 1969-1970 (Folder 65: 1)
  - Joint Economic Committee, 1969 (Folder 65: 2)
  - Jones, Emily L., 1969-1971 (Folder 65: 3)
  - Jordan, David C., 1971-1973 (Folder 65: 4)
  - Kaltefleiter, Werener, 1972-1973 (Folder 65: 5)
  - Kaplan, Morton A., 1967-1973 (Folder 65: 6)
  - Kirkendall, J. F., 1973 (Folder 66: 1)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1951-1973 (Folder 66: 2)
  - Klaiber, Wolfgang, 1971 (Folder 66: 3)
  - Kleinjans, Everett, 1973 (Folder 66: 4)
  - Kraemer, Fritz G. A., 1968-1973 (Folder 66: 5)
  - Kulish, Vasiliĭ M., 1970-1973 (Folder 66: 6)
  - Lanier, Addison, 1966-1972 (Folder 66: 7)
  - Larionov, Valentin, 1972 (Folder 66: 8)
  - Leibman, Morris I., 1970-1973 (Folder 66: 9)
  - Lodge, John Davis, 1968-1973 (Folder 66: 10)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1971 (Folder 66: 11)
  - A, 1959-1962 (Folder 67: 1)
  - Asilomar National Strategy Seminar, 1960 (Folder 67: 2)
  - B, 1960-1963 (Folder 67: 3-4)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 67: 3)
    - 1962-1963 (Folder 67: 4)
  - Barnett, Frank R., 1959-1963 (Folder 67-68)
    - 1959-1961 (Folder 67: 5)
    - 1962-1963 (Folder 68: 1)
  - Bell, Allyn R., Jr., 1960-1963 (Folder 68: 2)
  - C, 1960-1962 (Folder 68: 3-4)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 68: 3)
    - 1961-1962 (Folder 68: 4)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1958-1963 (Folder 68: 5)
  - D, 1958-1963 (Folder 68: 6-7)
    - 1958-1962 (Folder 68: 6)
    - 1962-1963 (Folder 68: 7)
  - E, 1958-1963 (Folder 68: 8)
  - F, 1958-1963 (Folder 68: 9)
  - Fisher, John M., 1961-1963 (Folder 68: 10)
  - Ford Foundation, 1956-1958 (Folder 69: 1)
  - G, 1960-1963 (Folder 69: 2-3)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 69: 2)
    - 1961-1963 (Folder 69: 3)
  - General Motors, 1961 (Folder 69: 4)
  - H, 1958-1961 (Folder 69: 5-6)
    - 1958-1959 (Folder 69: 5)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 69: 6)
  - Kornfeder, Joseph, 1958-1959 (Folder 69: 7)
  - M, 1958-1962 (Folder 69: 8-10)
    - 1958-1959 (Folder 69: 8)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 69: 9)
    - 1961-1962 (Folder 69: 10)
  - P, 1959-1961 (Folder 69: 11-12)
    - 1959-1960 (Folder 69: 11)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 69: 12)
  - Petrov, Vladimir, 1958-1959 (Folder 70: 1)
  - R, 1959-1963 (Folder 70: 2-5)
    - 1959-1960 (Folder 70: 2)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 70: 3)
    - 1962 (Folder 70: 4)
    - 1963 (Folder 70: 5)
  - Reinhardt, George C., 1958-1962 (Folder 70: 6)
  - Richardson Foundation, 1958-1963 (Folder 70: 7)
  - S, 1959-1963 (Folder 70: 8-10)
    - 1959-1960 (Folder 70: 8)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 70: 9)
    - 1961-1963 (Folder 70: 10)
  - Strausz-Hupé, Robert, 1960-1962 (Folder 71: 1)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1961-1963 (Folder 71: 2)
  - V, 1960-1963 (Folder 71: 3)
  - W, 1959-1963 (Folder 71: 4-6)
    - 1959-1960 (Folder 71: 4)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 71: 5)
    - 1962-1963 (Folder 71: 6)
  - X,Y,Z, 1959-1961 (Folder 71: 7)
  - A, 1981-1985 (Folder 72: 1)
  - Adams, Benson, 1972-1981 (Folder 72: 2)
  - Advanced International Studies Institute, 1983 (Folder 72: 3)
  - Allen, Richard, 1980-1983 (Folder 72: 4)
  - B, 1980-1982 (Folder 72: 5)
  - Barnett, Frank R., 1979-1983 (Folder 72: 6)
  - Bayrak, Murat, 1981 (Folder 72: 7)
  - Beilenson, Laurence W., 1981-1982 (Folder 72: 8)
  - BeLieu, Kenneth E., 1979-1980 (Folder 73: 1)
  - Black, Edwin F., 1981-1984 (Folder 73: 2)
  - Bolling, Landrum R., 1979-1982 (Folder 73: 3)
  - Brett, James Q., 1979 (Folder 73: 4)
  - C, 1980-1985 (Folder 73: 5-6)
    - 1980-1982 (Folder 73: 5)
    - 1982-1985 (Folder 73: 6)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1983-1985 (Folder 73: 7)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1981-1982 (Folder 73: 8)
  - China-related correspondence, 1979-1984 (Folder 73: 9)
  - Choudhury, Golam W., 1981 (Folder 74: 1)
  - Cindric, Cynthia, 1981 (Folder 74: 2)
  - Conference on European Problems, 1980-1985 (Folder 74: 3-4)
    - 1980 (Folder 74: 3)
    - 1981-1985 (Folder 74: 4)
  - Council of American Ambassadors, 1984-1985 (Folder 74: 5)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1980-1986 (Folder 74-75)
    - 1980-1981 (Folder 74: 6)
    - 1982-1986 (Folder 75: 1)
  - Corr, Edwin G., 1975-1985 (Folder 75: 2)
  - Crow, Trammell, 1982-1983 (Folder 75: 3)
  - D, 1980-1984 (Folder 75: 4)
  - Dice, Robert, 1981-1982 (Folder 75: 5)
  - E, 1980-1984 (Folder 75: 6)
  - Earhart Foundation, 1976-1983 (Folder 75: 7)
  - Enders, Thomas O., 1981-1982 (Folder 75: 8)
  - F, 1980-1983 (Folder 75: 9)
  - Fellowships, 1978-1981 (Folder 76: 1)
  - Ferguson, Glenn W., 1981 (Folder 76: 2)
  - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 1980-1985 (Folder 76: 3)
  - Foster, Richard B., 1980-1982 (Folder 76: 4)
  - Freedom House, 1980-1985 (Folder 76: 5-7)
    - 1980 (Folder 76: 5)
    - 1981-1982 (Folder 76: 6)
    - 1983-1985 (Folder 76: 7)
  - G, 1980-1986 (Folder 77: 1)
  - Goldberg, Sherwood, 1981-1982 (Folder 77: 2)
  - H, 1980-1986 (Folder 77: 3)
  - Haig, Alexander M., Jr., 1980-1982 (Folder 77: 4-5)
    - 1980 (Folder 77: 4)
    - 1981-1982 (Folder 77: 5)
  - Halterman, Rachel, 1980-1981 (Folder 78: 1)
  - Hanns-Seidel-Stiftung Institute for Political Cooperation, 1981-1982 (Folder 78: 2)
  - Heinz, John, 1977-1984 (Folder 78: 3)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1980-1984 (Folder 78: 4)
  - I, 1980-1982 (Folder 78: 5)
  - Ikle, Fred C., 1979-1982 (Folder 78: 6)
  - Institute of the USA and Canada, 1979-1982 (Folder 78: 7)
  - International Communications Agency, 1981 (Folder 79: 1)
  - International Management and Development Institute, 1981-1985 (Folder 79: 2)
  - Israel Research Institute of Contemporary Society, 1984 (Folder 79: 3)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board, 1983 (Folder 79: 4)
  - IU International Corporation, 1981 (Folder 79: 5)
  - Iungerich, Raphael, 1981 (Folder 79: 6)
  - J, 1980-1985 (Folder 79: 7)
  - Joint Economic Committee, 1980 (Folder 79: 8)
  - Jones, Emily L., 1979-1981 (Folder 80: 1)
  - K, 1980-1985 (Folder 80: 2)
  - Kalish, Harry, 1982 (Folder 80: 3)
  - Kase, Hideaki, 1981 (Folder 80: 4)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J., 1980-1983 (Folder 80: 5)
  - Kitiyakara, Plai, 1980-1983 (Folder 80: 6)
  - L, 1980-1985 (Folder 80: 7)
  - Lehman, John, 1982-1985 (Folder 80: 8)
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1980-1984 (Folder 80: 9)
  - M, 1979-1986 (Folder 81: 1)
  - Mednick, Sarnoff A., 1983 (Folder 81: 2)
  - Mensch, Ellen, 1981 (Folder 81: 3)
  - Methvin, Eugene, 1980-1985 (Folder 81: 4)
  - N, 1980-1982 (Folder 81: 5)
  - O, 1981-1983 (Folder 82: 1)
  - Oliver, Covey T., 1981-1985 (Folder 82: 2)
  - P, 1979-1983 (Folder 82: 3)
  - Pagan, Rafael, 1981-1982 (Folder 82: 4)
  - Philadelphia Committee on Foreign Policy, 1980-1985 (Folder 82: 5)
  - Poland-related correspondence, 1980-1981 (Folder 82: 6)
  - Policy Review, 1982 (Folder 82: 7)
  - President's Commission on White House Fellowships, 1983-1984 (Folder 82: 8)
  - R, 1980-1985 (Folder 82-83)
    - 1980-1982 (Folder 82: 9)
    - 1983-1985 (Folder 83: 1)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1980-1984 (Folder 83: 2)
  - Reagan administration, 1980-1984 (Folder 83: 3-4)
    - 1980-1981 (Folder 83: 3)
    - 1982-1984 (Folder 83: 4)
  - Regnery Gateway, Inc., 1982-1983 (Folder 83: 5)
  - Reinhardt, Gough, 1981 (Folder 83: 6)
  - Republican National Committee, 1979-1981 (Folder 83: 7)
  - Research proposals, 1984-1985 (Folder 83: 8)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1982-1983 (Folder 84: 1)
  - Rostow, Walt W., 1980-1983 (Folder 84: 2)
  - Rowny, Ed, 1980 (Folder 84: 3)
  - Rumsfeld, Donald H., 1979-1983 (Folder 84: 4)
  - S, 1980-1986 (Folder 84: 5-6)
    - 1980-1982 (Folder 84: 5)
    - 1983-1986 (Folder 84: 6)
  - Saltzman, Charles E., 1982-1984 (Folder 84: 7)
  - Salvatori, Henry, 1965-1985 (Folder 84: 8)
  - Sicherman, Harvey, 1981-1982 (Folder 84: 9)
  - Silver, Arnold, 1981 (Folder 84: 10)
  - Smith Kline Corporation, 1979-1983 (Folder 85: 1)
  - South Africa, 1979-1982 (Folder 85: 2)
  - SRI International, 1983-1984 (Folder 85: 3)
  - Steele, George P., 1981-1982 (Folder 85: 4)
  - Strausz-Hupé, Robert, 1979-1984 (Folder 85: 5)
  - Suchlicki, Jaime, 1979-1985 (Folder 85: 6)
  - T, 1982-1985 (Folder 86: 1)
  - Thompson, W. Scott, 1982-1983 (Folder 86: 2)
  - Trager, Frank N., 1982 (Folder 86: 3)
  - Trips, 1981 (Folder 86: 4-7)
  - Tufts University, 1981-1983 (Folder 86: 8)
  - U, 1980-1984 (Folder 86: 9)
  - United States Global Strategy Council, 1983 (Folder 86: 10)
  - United States Industrial Council, 1981 (Folder 86: 11)
  - University of Oklahoma Press, 1981-1983 (Folder 86: 12)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1980-1985 (Folder 87-88)
    - 1980 (Folder 87: 1-2)
    - 1980-1981 (Folder 87: 3)
    - 1981 (Folder 87: 4)
    - 1982-1985 (Folder 88: 1)
  - V, 1980-1983 (Folder 88: 2)
  - W, 1979-1984 (Folder 88: 3)
  - Walker, Diane, 1980-1985 (Folder 88: 4)
  - Watson, Stanley, 1981-1984 (Folder 88: 5)
  - White House Fellowships, 1984-1985 (Folder 89: 1)
  - World Strategy Network, 1984 (Folder 89: 2)
  - X, 1980-1985 (Folder 89: 3)
  - Y, 1980-1985 (Folder 89: 4)
  - Z, 1980-1985 (Folder 89: 5)
  - Zawodny, Jay K., 1980-1981 (Folder 89: 6)
  - Zemtsov, Ilya, 1980-1984 (Folder 89: 7)
  - Zimmerman, Robert F., 1980-1981 (Folder 89: 8)
  - University of Pennsylvania teaching file, 1976-1985 (Folder 89-90)
    - Exams, 1976-1983 (Folder 89: 9)
    - Grades, 1980-1984 (Folder 89-90)
      - 1980 (Folder 89: 10)
      - 1980 (Folder 90: 1)
      - 1981-1984 (Folder 90: 2)
    - Recommendations, 1980-1985 (Folder 90: 3)
    - Syllabi, 1979-1984 (Folder 90: 4)
- Speeches and Writings, 1976-1984 (Folder 91-92)
  - Study of the Soviet military, 1976 (Folder 91: 1)
  - "Toward a New Concept of Atlantic Partnership,", 1976 (Folder 91: 2)
  - "US Policy Interests in the Asian-Pacific Area, the US Purpose in Asia,", 1976 (Folder 91: 3)
  - "Carter's Confusing Defense Program,", 1978 (Folder 91: 4)
  - "China, Japan, and the Question of Western Security,", 1980 (Folder 91: 5)
  - "How Not to Deter Nuclear War,", 1980 (Folder 91: 6)
  - "Long-term Realities in Sino-American Relations,", 1982 (Folder 91: 7)
  - "Reducing the Likelihood of a Nuclear War,", 1982 (Folder 91: 8)
  - "The Significance of Nuclear Weapons Accuracy,", 1982 (Folder 91: 9)
  - "Choke Points, Maritime Strategy and the Geopolitical Balance of Tomorrow,", 1983 (Folder 91: 10)
  - Soviet Global Strategy, 1983-1984 (Folder 92: 1-2)
    - First draft, 1983 (Folder 92: 1)
    - Second draft, 1984 (Folder 92: 2)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1976-1981 (Folder 93: 1)
- Pamphlets and reports, 1974-1985 (Folder 93: 2-14)